{
    "subject": "Kamal_Haasan",
    "predicate": "created",
    "object": "Thevar_Magan",
    "human_readable": "Kamal Haasan created Thevar Magan.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.7455941438674927,
            "question": "Who created the movie Thevar Magan?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5347349047660828,
            "question": "Is Kamal Haasan known for acting and directing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.40396928787231445,
            "question": "What is the name of the film directed by Kamal Haasan?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.35515448451042175,
            "question": "What genre might Thevar Magan belong to based on its director?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.348381370306015,
            "question": "How has Kamal Haasan's work influenced Indian cinema?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34423011541366577,
            "question": "What themes might be explored in a film like Thevar Magan?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34351179003715515,
            "question": "What year was Thevar Magan likely released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3188880681991577,
            "question": "Are there any actors known for working with Kamal Haasan in his films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3099344074726105,
            "question": "Can you name other films directed by Kamal Haasan?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.027712929993867874,
            "question": "What are some popular Tamil films of that era?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Kamal Haasan created Thevar Magan.",
            "html": "yago_3082_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name other films directed by Kamal Haasan?",
            "html": "yago_3082_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any actors known for working with Kamal Haasan in his films?",
            "html": "yago_3082_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What year was Thevar Magan likely released?",
            "html": "yago_3082_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_3082_128.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_3082_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_3082_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_3082_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_3082_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_3082_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_3082_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_3082_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_3082_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_3082_83.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provided contain information about Kamal Haasan's film \"Thevar Magan\", including its release year (1992), director (Bharathan), and plot. Additionally, one of the documents mentions that Kamal Haasan has officially announced a sequel to Thevar Magan, indicating that he was involved in creating the original film. Therefore, the information supports the triple that Kamal Haasan created Thevar Magan."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents confirm that Kamal Haasan was involved in the creation of \"Thevar Magan,\" as evidenced by statements like, \"Written by Kamal Haasan and directed by Malayalam filmmaker Bharathan, Thevar Magan won five National awards and was selected as India\u2019s official entry to the Oscars.\" Therefore, the information supports the statement that Kamal Haasan created \"Thevar Magan.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}